http://www.stoeverglass.com/privacy-statement

Skip to content
Privacy Statement
Privacy Statementstoever2020-11-16T13:48:06+00:00
To help the government fight the funding of terrorism and money laundering activities, federal law requires that we verify the identity of every person who maintains or controls an account with Stoever Glass.
Stoever Glass does not sell, rent or license your personal information to any non-affiliated persons or entities. We use your personal information to provide services to you. We may disclose your personal information, as permitted by law, to non-affiliated third parties that provide financial services to you. All third parties we use for record retention are required to protect personal information in a manner similar to the way we protect personal information.
We will disclose personal information to government and regulatory agencies and to comply with a lawful summons, court order, subpoena, fraud investigation, audit or regulatory examination.
Affiliate Sharing for Marketing Purposes
You may limit our affiliates in marketing their products or services to you based on personal information that we collect about you and share with them. Your choice to limit marketing offers from our affiliates will apply until you tell us to change your choice. You can opt back in at any time.
To limit affiliate marketing offers by contacting Roland Stoever(Roland@stoeverglass.com) An opt-out election made by one account owner of a Joint account is applicable to all account owners of the Joint account.
An opt-out election must be made for each separate account you hold at Stover Glass, Inc. and Stoever Glass Wealth Management.
Toggle NavigationINFO@STOEVERGLASS.COM800.223.3881 (NEW YORK)844.345.1544 (BOCA RATON)CLIENT LOGINLEGAL DISCLOSURESPRIVACY STATEMENTBOND HUBMembers FINRA/SIPCFINRA’s Brokercheck
©Copyright 2020 | Stoever Glass & Co. All rights reserved. | Powered by Electrum Branding
Go to Top
